Cooperative Recreation Service collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3. Production Files/Custom Songbook Files, ca. 1932-2008
  - Having Fun the Polish Way, ca. 1952-1981 (Box-folder 75/8)
    Correspondence about the Polish American custom songbook, Having Fun the Polish Way.
  - Hawaii, Aloha Songs, ca. 1953-1967 (Box-folder 75/9)
    Includes Hawaiian Sampler and Aloha Sampler custom songbooks, as well as correspondence, notes, and song lists from Hawaii churches and organizations.
  - Hawaiian Sampler, ca. 1963-1967 (Box-folder 75/10)
    Includes Aloha Sampler custom songbook and song master negatives.
  - Hearts Full of Song (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1983-2011 (Box-folder 75/11)
    Includes Hearts Full of Song custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, permissions, invoices, and notes.
  - Hearts Full of Song (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1978-1984 (Box-folder 75/12)
    Copyright information, notes, song lists, and correspondence.
  - Hearts Full of Song, Revisions, ca. 2010-2011 (Box-folder 76/1)
    Notes, correspondence, and song sheets relating to a revisions for a reprint of the Hearts Full of Song custom songbook.
  - Hoosier Copyrights, ca. 2002-2003 (Box-folder 76/2)
    Copyright and permission information for songs for the Girl Scouts of Hoosier Capital custom songbook.
  - Hymns for Today, James Carley, ca. 1960-1969 (Box-folder 76/3)
    Hymns for Today custom songbook, related correspondence with James Carley, and song lists and notes.
  - Hymns of the Month, ca. 1979-1981 (Box-folder 76/4)
    Correspondence with the National Federation of Music Clubs about the Hymns of the Month booklet.
  - Hymns of Universal Praise, ca. 1978-1979 (Box-folder 76/5)
    Copyrights, permissions, correspondence, and song sheets related to the Hymns of Universal Praise custom songbook.
  - Illinois Federation of Women's Clubs (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1976-1978 (Box-folder 76/6)
    Inlcudes three copies of Songs for Illinois Clubwomen custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, notes, and lists.
  - Illinois Federation of Women's Clubs (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1964-1978 (Box-folder 76/7)
    Includes correspondence, song lists, song sheets, song master negatives, and notes.
  - India choir, etc., ca. 1955-1959 (Box-folder 76/8)
    Includes various versions of Joyful Songs of India, as well as song lists, Hindi song sheet music and lyrics, and India choir information.
    - India, ca. 1955-1960, AFC 2016/051: SR03; 5-inch open reel tape
      Includes 15 songs. Tape being treated for mold.
  - Indiana 4-H songbook, ca. 1955-1969 (Box-folder 76/9)
    Correspondence with Purdue University staff, invoices, and permissions information.
  - Indiana Sings, ca. 1976-1981 (Box-folder 76/10)
    Indiana Sings custom songbook, as well as related correspondence.
  - "It's Me, O Lord," ca. 1992 (Box-folder 76/11)
    Larry Eisenberg publication and notes.
  - Itinerary in Song, ca. 1960-1963 (Box-folder 76/12)
    Includes different versions of Itinerary in Song custom songbook, as well as song lists and indexes and notes.
  - Joyful Noise correspondence, ca. 1987-1989 (Box-folder 77/1)
    Includes correspondence with Helen and Larry Eisenberg, as well as loose song sheets.
  - Joyful Noise covers and intro, ca. 1989-1994 (Box-folder 77/2)
    Corrrespondence, license, copyrights, song indexes, cover drafts, and introduction to Joyful Noise custom songbook.
  - Joyful Noise permissions, ca. 1988-1993 (Box-folder 77/3)
    Licenses, permissions, and publishing agreements.
  - Joyful Noise songs, ca. 1985-1995 (Box-folder 77/4)
    Includes loose song sheets and lists.
  - Joyful Noise/the Eisenbergs (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1988-1991 (Box-folder 77/5)
    Includes correspondence with Helen and Larry Eisenberg, as well as billing statements, cost analyses for publication, and notes.
  - Joyful Noise/the Eisenbergs (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1993-1997 (Box-folder 77/6)
    Includes correspondence with Helen and Larry Eisenberg, as well as correspondence, song lists, and copyright, license and permissions information.
  - Joyful Noise/the Eisenbergs (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1993-1998 (Box-folder 77/7)
    Includes correspondence, rights and permissions information, and information about proposed revisions for Make a Joyful Noise custom songbook.
  - Joyful Singing, ca. 1966-1985 (Box-folder 77/8)
    Includes copies of Joyful Singing custom songbook, as well as related permissions, correspondence, invoices, and licenses.
  - Joyful Songs of India, ca. 1956 (Box-folder 77/9)
    Includes custom songbooks and song master negatives.
  - Nancy Joyner, correspondence, ca. 1976 (Box-folder 77/10)
  - Junior High Sing, ca. 1965-1966 (Box-folder 78/1)
    Various editions of Junior High Sing, related correspondence, notes, and annotated song lists.
  - Kathryn Klinger, ca. 1985 (Box-folder 78/2)
    Includes Sing a Green Valley custom songbook, and related correspondence, invoices, song lists, song sheets, and notes.
  - Labor songs, ca. 1943-1947 (Box-folder 99/4)
    Includes "Meadowland (Cavalry of the Steppes)" and other sheet music.
  - Lake Erie Girl Scout Council, ca. 1986-1987 (Box-folder 78/3)
    Includes Celebration Song Book custom songbook, and related invoices, correspondence, shipping labels, song lists, song sheets, and notes.
  - Let's Sing, ca. 1990-1991 (Box-folder 78/4)
    Includes Let's Sing custom songbook, as well as related license agreements, permission requests, and correspondence.
  - License - Morning Has Broken, ca. 1958, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 78/5)
  - Licenses/paid orders (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1985-1986 (Box-folder 78/6)
    Includes Songs for Camps and Reunions custom songbook, licenses, permissions, publishing agreements, and correspondence.
  - Licenses/paid orders (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1985-1986 (Box-folder 78/7)
    Includes annotated song sheets, licenses, permissions, publishing agreements, and correspondence.
  - Life on the H2O, ca. 1964-1970 (Box-folder 78/8)
    Includes two copies of Life on the H2O custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, research, and notes.
  - Lift Every Voice, ca. 1953-1988 (Box-folder 78/9)
    Lift Every Voice accompaniment edition (copyright, 1953).
  - Lift Up Your Voices (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1980-1981 (Box-folder 79/1)
    Includes CGIT custom songbook, as well as related correspondence with Canadian Girls in Training (CGIT) and information about a new songbook for CGIT.
  - Lift Up Your Voices (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1980-1981 (Box-folder 79/2)
    Includes information about CGIT, sheet music, and lyric sheets, correspondence, and notes.
  - Lift Up Your Voices (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1966-1979 (Box-folder 79/3)
    Includes Lift Your Voices Again custom songbooks, cover designs, information about orders of books, song lists, shipping statements, and correspondence.
  - Lutheran Marriage Encounter, ca. 1983-1997 (Box-folder 79/4)
    Includes notes, song sheets, song lists, and copyright information for the Lutheran Marriage Encounter custom songbook.
  - Marin County GSC, ca. 1986-1987 (Box-folder 79/5)
    Includes cover design for Marin Sings: 15 Years of Girl Scout Music custom songbook, as well as song lists, indexes, royalty information, invoices and research.
  - Marlu-Ridge, Jefferson, Maryland, ca. 1966-1978 (Box-folder 79/6)
    Includes Mar-lu-Ridge Songbook custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, song lists, indexes, and information about a reprint of the songbook.
  - Merry Hours, ca. 1957-2007 (Box-folder 79/7)
    Includes Merry Hours: Favorite Hungarian Folk Songs custom songbook and related correspondence.
  - Methodist Men in Indiana (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1965-1981 (Box-folder 79/8)
    Includes licenses, song sheets, permission requests, invoices, notes, correspondence related to Happiness is a Song and New Horizons custom songbooks.
  - Methodist Men in Indiana (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1965-1978 (Box-folder 79/9)
    Includes song lists, permission requests, invoices, notes, correspondence related to Happiness is a Song and New Horizons custom songbooks.
  - Methodist Men, East Pennsylvania, ca. 1980-1981 (Box-folder 79/10)
    Includes Convocation Song Book custom songbook, as well as cover designs, correspondence, and invoices for book orders.
  - Mile Hi Girl Scouts Council, ca. 1982-1992 (Box-folder 79/11)
    Includes permission requests, license agreements, quotes, and correspondence related to the Sing a Mile Hi custom songbook.
  - Mile High Council (Denver) Girl Scouts, ca. 1980-1991 (Box-folder 80/1)
    Includes notes, correspondence, sheet music, song lists, and a cover design for Sing a Mile High custom songbook.
  - Mile High GSC - Sing a Mile Hi, ca. 1996 (Box-folder 80/2)
    Includes the reprint of Sing a Mile Hi custom songbook, as well as correspondence, information about royalties, copyrights, and song sheets.
  - Minnesota 4-H Club Songbooks, ca. 1987-1988 (Box-folder 80/3)
    Includes two versions of the reprints of the Minnesota 4-H Songbook custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, copyright information, and notes.
  - Miscellaneous Stock Book permissions, ca. 1978 (Box-folder 80/4)
    Includes correspondence, notes, and copyright information about reprints of custom songbooks.
  - Mohawk Pathways Girl Scout Council (folder 1 of 3), ca. 1984-1988 (Box-folder 80/5)
    Includes two copies of Song Bag: Mohawk Pathways Girl Scout Council custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, song lists and indexes, permission requests, shipping charts, notes, and song sheets.
  - Mohawk Pathways Girl Scout Council (folder 2 of 3), ca. 1983-1984 (Box-folder 80/6)
    Permission information, song lists, correspondence, and song sheets for Mohawk Pathways Girl Scout Council songbook.
  - Mohawk Pathways Girl Scout Council (folder 3 of 3), ca. 1982-1984 (Box-folder 80/7)
    Includes permission and copyright information, songsheets, correspondence, and notes.
  - Jean Moore/Let's Sing, ca. 1979-1993 (Box-folder 81/1)
    Includes three copies of Let's Sing custom songbook, as well as rights and permissions information, correspondence, invoices, and notes.
  - Mo-Ranch, ca. 1986 (Box-folder 81/2)
    Includes correspondence, song lists, invoices, copyright and permissions information, and notes for the Mo-Ranch Presbyterian Camp songbook.
  - Lee Morgan and Elizabeth Morgan, correspondence, ca. 1967-1968 (Box-folder 81/3)
  - Music Shall Live, undated (Box-folder 81/4)
    Music Shall Live custom songbook.
  - National Marriage Encounter Conference correspondence, ca. 1991-1992 (Box-folder 81/5)
    Includes a custom book contract, song indexes, correspondence, and song sheets.
  - National Marriage Encounter Copy, ca. 1991-1992 (Box-folder 81/6)
    Includes sheet music and cover design for Light the Candle custom song book.
  - National Marriage Encounter copyrights, ca. 1991-1992 (Box-folder 81/7)
    Includes license requests, copyright information, and correspondence relating to the Light the Candle custom songbook.
  - National Methodists; Part of Singing the Lord's Song (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1982-1983 (Box-folder 81/8)
    Includes Singing the Lord's Song custom songbook, and related correspondence, shipping charts, song lists, invoices, and notes.
  - National Methodists; Part of Singing the Lord's Song (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1981-1982 (Box-folder 81/9)
    Includes notes, correspondence, and annotated song lists.
  - New Jersey Board of the Laity, Southern New Jersey Methodist Conference, ca. 1976-1979 (Box-folder 81/10)
    Including United Methodists Sing custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, permissions information, song indexes, and notes.
  - Newaygo copyright check lists, ca. 2001 (Box-folder 82/1)
    Includes annotated song lists related to the Camp Newaygo custom songbook.
  - Newaygo, correspondence, ca. 1986-2001 (Box-folder 82/2)
    Correspondence and permissions information for the reprint of the Newaygo custom songbook.
  - Newaygo permissions, ca. 1986 (Box-folder 82/3)
    Correspondence, permissions information, shipping information, song lyrics, and notes related to the reprint of the Newaygo custom songbook.
  - Newaygo permissions for "Pass it On," 1986, 2001 (Box-folder 82/4)
  - Newaygo Sings (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1986, 2001 (Box-folder 82/5)
    Song sheets from Camp Newaygo Sings and cover design for Camp Newaygo Sings II.
  - Newaygo Sings (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1986 (Box-folder 82/6)
    Draft of Camp Newaygo Sings.
  - Newaygo Sings II, ca. 2001 (Box-folder 82/7)
    Camp Newaygo Sings II custom songbook.
  - North Carolina Lutheran Marriage Encounter, ca. 1991 (Box-folder 82/8)
    Permissions, copyright information, and correspondence related to NC Lutheran Marriage Encounter.
  - North Indiana Conference, United Methodist Church, ca. 1979-1982 (Box-folder 82/9)
    Includes two editions of Sing...For the World Needs a Song... custom songbook, invoices, correspondence, shipping information, song sheets, and permissions information.
  - Northern Tier High Adventure, Ely, Minnesota, ca. 1998 (Box-folder 82/10)
    Includes correspondence, permissions, royalty, and license information, and invoices.
  - Ohio United Church of Christ (folder 1 of 4), ca. 1983-1985 (Box-folder 82/11)
    Includes three copies of Songs From the Hills custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, song lists and indexes, shipping information and invoices, and notes.
  - Ohio United Church of Christ (folder 2 of 4), ca. 1983-1984 (Box-folder 82/12)
    Includes correspondence, licensing information, song sheets and sheet music, invoices, and notes.
  - Ohio United Church of Christ (folder 3 of 4), ca. 1983 (Box-folder 83/1)
    Includes layouts and cover designs for Songs From the Hills custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, song lists, licenses, publishing agreements, and notes.
  - Ohio United Church of Christ (folder 4 of 4), ca. 1981-1983 (Box-folder 83/2)
    Includes correspondence, song lists, shipping information, invoices, song sheets, sheet music, and notes.
  - Ohio UCC, ca. 1994 (Box-folder 83/3)
    Includes song lists, correspondence, and permission and copyright information for the Ohio United Church of Christ.
  - Ohio UCC copyrights, ca. 1993-1994 (Box-folder 83/4)
    Permissions, copyright, license, and royalty information for Ohio United Church of Christ.
  - Old Custom Extras, ca. 1987 (Box-folder 83/5)
    Includes Children's Songs for a Friendly Planet custom songs book, and related shipping information, song sheets and pages from songbooks.
  - One in Song, ca. 1963-1969 (Box-folder 83/6)
    Includes One in Song custom songbooks, correspondence, song sheets and pages from songbooks, and permissions information.
  - One Tune More, ca. 1961 (Box-folder 83/7)
    One Tune More custom songbooks, indexes, and permission request.
  - Original copies of songs, ca. 1966-1990 (Box-folder 83/8)
    Includes song sheets, pages from songbooks, and notes.
  - Oxford University Press, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 84/1)
    Shipping information from Oxford University Press.
  - Pacific Northwest Methodist (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1980 (Box-folder 84/2)
    Shipping information, song lyrics, song sheets, parts of songbooks, song indexes, correspondence, permissions information, and notes related to Our Northwest Sings! custom songbook.
  - Pacific Northwest Methodist (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1956-1980 (Box-folder 84/3)
    Includes correspondence, song lists, permissions information, and notes related to Our Northwest Sings! custom songbook.
  - Pacific Northwest Methodist, Our Northwest Sings!, ca. 1965-1981 (Box-folder 84/4)
    Three copies of Our Northwest Sings! custom songbook and related correspondence.
  - Pacific Northwest Methodist, Seattle permissions, Our Northwest Sings!, ca. 1979-1980 (Box-folder 84/5)
    Permissions, correspondence, and other related information about Our Northwest Sings! custom songbook.
  - Pagoda, ca. 1953-1978 (Box-folder 84/6)
    Copies of The Pagoda custom songbook, as well as portions of the songbook, sheet music, song indexes, and correspondence.
  - Paid invoices and statements, ca. 1981-1982 (Box-folder 84/7)
    Includes correspondence, permissions agreements, song sheets, copyright information, and notes.
  - Palos Verde School District, ca. 1993-1998 (Box-folder 84/8)
    Copies of Songs From Our Heritage custom songbook, as well as cover designs, song lists, permissions information, and copyright information.
  - Peace Corps, ca. 1964-1968 (Box-folder 84/9)
    Includes invoices, correspondence, and permissions information related to the Peace Corps Packet Folk Songs.
  - Penn 4-H, ca. 1981-1991 (Box-folder 84/10)
    Includes Songs From the Keystone State custom songbook, as well as related correspondence.
  - Penn Wood's Girl Scout Council, ca. 1992-1993 (Box-folder 84/11)
    Song lists and correspondence from the Penn Wood's Girl Scout Council.
  - Pennsylvania 4-H (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1981 (Box-folder 85/1)
    Includes Songs for the Keystone State custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, royalty information, and notes.
  - Pennsylvania 4-H (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1953-1981 (Box-folder 85/2)
    Includes Songs for the Keystone State custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, shipping information, invoices, and notes.
  - Permian Basin, ca. 1988-2000 (Box-folder 85/3)
    Notes, correspondence, royalty information, and permissions information related to the Let's Sing custom songbook for the Permian Basin Girl Scout Council.
  - Permian Basin Girl Scout Council, ca. 1970-1981 (Box-folder 85/4)
  - Permissions for 2001 Ed. Camp Newaygo Sings II, ca. 1986-2001 (Box-folder 85/5)
    Permissions, licensing, royalty, and publishing information for Camp Newaygo songbooks.
  - Permissions for KumbaYa, Marvin V. Frey (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1956-1981 (Box-folder 99/5)
    Permissions agreements, correspondence, songbook, song sheets, and hearing information for Marvin Frey.
  - Permissions for KumbaYa, Marvin V. Frey (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1957-1979 (Box-folder 99/6)
  - Permissions, World Around Songs, ca. 1976 (Box-folder 85/6)
    Permissions information and notes for World Around Songs.
  - Personnel/Employment (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1971 (Box-folder 85/7)
    Pamphlets and journals related to employment laws in North Carolina.
  - Personnel/Employment (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1977 (Box-folder 85/8)
    Includes notes and correspondence.
  - The Philip Lief Group, 1997 (Box-folder 85/9)
    Information about the Philip Lief Group, an independent book development company.
  - Philippine Song Book, ca. 1962-1967 (Box-folder 85/10)
    Correspondence, notes, sheet music, and song lists related to Tayo'y Umawit custom songbook.
  - Pioneer Clubs printing, ca. 1978-1990 (Box-folder 86/1)
    Correspondence, shipping, printing, and license information for the Pioneer Clubs.
  - Pioneer Girls, undated (Box-folder 86/2)
    Song sheets and song master negatives from Pioneer Girls custom songbook.
  - Pioneer Girls/Pioneer original permissions (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1976-1984 (Box-folder 86/3)
    Includes New Festival Sounds custom songbook, as well as related book designs, indexes, invoices, song sheets, and correspondence.
  - Pioneer Girls/Pioneer original permissions (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1976-1984 (Box-folder 86/4)
    Includes Songfest and New Festival Sounds custom songbooks, as well as related correspondence, song indexes, permissions information, notes.
  - A Pocket Full of Songs, undated (Box-folder 86/5)
    Includes copies of A Pocket Full of Songs custom songbook, song master negatives, and song indexes.
  - Pocket Hymnal reprint, 1979 (Box-folder 86/6)
    Permissions information and song master negatives for Pocket Hymnal and 88 Top Songs custom songbooks.
  - Pocketfull of Songs, ca. 1988 (Box-folder 86/7)
    Correspondence and copyright information for Pocketfull of Songs custom songbook.
  - Polish Folk Songs, Leona Lorenz, ca. 1963-1969 (Box-folder 86/8)
    Copies of A Sampler of Polish Folk Songs custom songbook, as well as related song sheets, song proofs, song indexes, and song lyrics.
  - Proof books, undated (Box-folder 86/9)
    Song indexes, cover designs, lists, and two custom songbooks, A Chance to Sing and All Sing.
  - Public Domain songs, ca. 1989-1991 (Box-folder 86/10)
    Includes correspondence and copyright information.
  - Jean Putnam, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 86/11)
    Correspondence between Jean Putnam and World Around Songs.
  - Redlands G.S. reprint, 1986-1995 (Box-folder 86/12)
    Includes three copies of Songs of Gold (Red Lands Council of Girl Scouts) custom songbook, as well as related correspondence, permission and copyright information.
  - Redlands Girl Scouts, ca. 1979-1985 (Box-folder 86/13)
    Correspondence, permission and copyright information, and notes related to the Red Lands Council of Girl Scouts.
  - Rev. Art Allen Iowa Methodists (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1980-1981 (Box-folder 87/1)
    Includes New Horizons custom songbook, and related permissions and copyright information, correspondence, song sheets, and notes.
  - Rev. Art Allen Iowa Methodists (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1978 (Box-folder 87/2)
    Includes correspondence with Rev. Art Allen, as well as permissions and copyright information.
  - Jean Ritchie (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1960-1968 (Box-folder 87/3)
    Correspondence between Jean Ritchie and Lynn Rohrbough.
  - Jean Ritchie (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1962-1969 (Box-folder 87/4)
  - River Bluffs GS Council, ca. 1980-1990 (Box-folder 87/5)
    Includes Songs You Love to Sing custom songbook, as well as related song lists, indexes, book layouts and designs, and correspondence.
  - Lynn Rohrbough, ca. 1963-1980 (Box-folder 87/6)
    Includes correspondence and material related to the Cooperative Recreation Service business.
  - Lynn Rohrbough, correspondence (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1959-1970 (Box-folder 87/7)
    Correspondence by and with Lynn Rohrbough, including with Olcutt and Phyllis Sanders from Bogota, Colombia.
  - Lynn Rohrbough, correspondence (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1948-1958 (Box-folder 87/8)
    Correspondence by and with Lynn and Katherine Rohrbough, including with Olcutt and Phyllis Sanders about songbooks and personal matters. Includes three photographic prints.
  - Rohrbough family, ca. 1990-1991 (Box-folder 87/9)
    Includes correspondence, and Family Songs: Rohrbough Lynch Reunion, San Diego 1991 songbook.
  - Sacred Canons, ca. 1966-1991 (Box-folder 87/10)
    Includes two copies of Sacred Canons custom songbook, as well as related copyright registrations, permissions, and cover designs.
  - Tony Saletan, ca. 1957-1969 (Box-folder 87/11)
    Correspondence with Tony Saletan, American folk singer and educator.
  - A Sampler of Japanese Songs, undated (Box-folder 88/1)
    Includes A Sampler of Japanese Songs custom songbook, song master negatives, and drafts of the songbook.
  - Sampler Sixty, undated (Box-folder 88/2)
    Includes Sampler Sixty custom songbook and song master negatives.
  - San Fernando Girl Scout Council, ca. 1985-1986 (Box-folder 88/3)
    Includes correspondence, permissions, and copyright information.
  - G. Schirmer, ca. 1976-1978 (Box-folder 88/4)
    Includes One in Song custom songbook, as well as related permissions information from G. Schirmer, Inc.
  - Schlingman, E.L., ca. 1964-1972 (Box-folder 88/5)
    Includes correspondence with Ed. L. Schirmer of United Church Board for Homeland Ministries.
  - The Score for '64, ca. 1962-1964 (Box-folder 88/6)
    Includes song indexes and song master negatives.
  - Scranton Pocono Girl Scout Council, ca. 1969-1980 (Box-folder 88/7)
    Includes The Council Songbook custom songbook, as well as related song indexes, song sheets, correspondence, invoices, and notes.
  - Seal of Ohio Girl Scout Council (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1995-1996 (Box-folder 88/8)